Hey guys, my name is Igor and I'm a Product Engineer.
I found out about Stir while listening to the Means of Creation podcast with Joe.
Man! I was so impressed by it.
I saw how you guys went above and beyond to help creators grow their businesses.
From helping airrack reaching 1 million subscribers to helping Mixer streamers
migrate their followers.
You guys show a customer obsession that I also share.
I've been following creators for more than 10 years now.
I still remember the time from Taking the Hobbits to Isengard...
Nyan Cat...
Rick Roll...
And following the early days of Smosh and MysteryGuitarMan.
I'm so obsessed with creators that I'm actually even dating and living
with one.
And that's me.
I started working in the creator economy more than three years ago when I joined LBRY.
A startup that helps create their own and sell their content by having it published
on a blockchain.
Sometime later, I co-founded Odeon which is a video platform that helps creators
bundle their subscription offering with other creators.
We worked relentlessly full-time for almost three years with creators on our side.
I recently left Odeon.
However, I still believe there's a lot to be built to satisfy the growing
needs of creators.
Startup founders already have a lot of infrastructure to help them build
and grow their business.
There is Stripe Atlas for helping start a company and Y Combinator for helping grow.
Creators don't have all of that...
Yet.
But it's only a question of time until they get the same level of support than
startup founders.
And Stir is perfectly positioned to move the needle in that direction.
A see Stir beeing at the forefront of that vision.
And that's why I want to work alongside with you to make that reality happen.
I have years of experience in building products for creators.
From helping design features on Figma.
To architecture an API on Node.js.
I've set up cloud infrastructures.
And handled operations in a startup.
I'm frequently talking with creators and interviewing them.
That helps me empathize with the problems they frequently encounter.
If I would get the opportunity to work alongside you, I would make sure to keep
that habbit.
That way I can also get early feedback and iterate faster with them.
I would help proactively.
Startup have diverse and often changing needs.
Switching roles has never been an issue for me.
If there's a problem with the servers.
I would be the one jumping right into it to solve it.
I hope this video finds you well, and that we get the chance to meet and talk
more about how I would provide value to you and the creators.
See ya.